<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mohammed Essaid MEZERREG</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mohammed Essaid MEZERREG</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Hugo to Astro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/leaving-hugo-to-astro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/leaving-hugo-to-astro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since I bought this domain, I&amp;rsquo;ve tested countless SSGs (Static Site Generators). I used Jekyll, Gatsby, Nexo, Next.js, and others. I never finished any of those versions—I switched between them because I have new ideas all the time. New ideas come with checking the right tools to release them, but as always, the will to do the actual work fades away in the searching phase. So, I never finished any of them nor used the acquired skills professionally; in fact, I dropped them the moment my will to continue vanished.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Host Hugo in Vercel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-to-host-hugo-in-vercel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-to-host-hugo-in-vercel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to go with &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; to build my personal &lt;a href=&#34;https://mohessaid.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;. The only thing I based my choice on was the build time. I thought Hugo was in the same league as &lt;a href=&#34;https://astro.new&#34;&gt;Astro&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to content management perks, but it isn&amp;rsquo;t quite there yet. Or, I can say it has its own path since it&amp;rsquo;s older than most of the other static site generators I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered. Moreover, it&amp;rsquo;s a Go application, which is another important factor to consider when evaluating technology choices.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Expirement on Writing Platforms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/writing-platforms-expirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/writing-platforms-expirement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided to run a little expirement on writing platforms. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the right article until I faced an issue building this website on Vercel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I published a post on how I fixed the issue on different platforms online. This idea came to mind after seeing some posts doing well on &lt;a href=&#34;https://mohessaid.medium.com&#34;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt;. So I wanted to try other paltforms as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will update this post every other day to see how the stats are doing. Also, how the race for the first spot in search results is going.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I Follow in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/following-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:37:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/following-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Around 7:00 a.m today. I checked on LinkedIn out of curiousity to see what&amp;rsquo;s going on.&#xA;I stumbled on this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/bassemdghaidy_programming-coding-softwareengineering-ugcPost-7258865232326934528-jiZS&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; where Bassem Dghaidi shared his list of recommended books and channels on YouTube.&#xA;I know some of what he shared in his list. However, I wanted to share what I find&#xA;worthy of following. I started writing a comment on  his post. However, the list&#xA;kept growing. Since I live by the rule Scott Henslman once mentioned in his blog.&#xA;When you write an email, comment to somebody and it becomes longer than it should.&#xA;Post it as a blog post and share it with him and whoever want that information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding SVG Logo to Hugo!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/journal/001_logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 10:43:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/journal/001_logo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I tried to add my SVG logo to the header of this website. I found some solutions, but they didn&amp;rsquo;t work for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
